​​​ ​♫ Old fortune teller ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ Gave me playing cards, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ And eight clones appeared in this world, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ And every one of them Is different, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ All different colors, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ All different views​ ​​
​​ ​On all sorts of stuff ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ Who’s the king, and who’s the jack, ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ No two of them are alike ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ What could possibly go wrong? ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​♫ EVERYTHING WENT WRONG! ♫​ ​​
​​​ ​Whatcha waaatchin’?​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to...​ ​​
​​​ ​ROCK AND ROLL!!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way! We’re not watching this crap today!​ ​​
​​​ ​Give it back!..​ ​​
​​​ ​But it’s my turn today!​ ​​
​​​ ​Waru! We never took turns!​ ​​
​​​ ​Give it...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, Spade. Give me the remote!​ ​​
​​​ ​You never watch TV anyway.​ ​​
​​​ ​I am tonight!​ ​​
​​​ ​They’re showing the 16th century Ottoman-Hungarian War on “Epoch-TV”.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, turn it up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ugh, not more power struggles!​ ​​
​​​ ​We watch TV to become stupider, not smarter!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are there concubines in this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Spade, don’t give him the remote!​ ​​
​​​ ​Or he’ll put on his soap operas for housewives!​ ​​
​​​ ​They’re not just for housewives,​ ​​
​​ ​but also for divorced men in their 30s!​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh… what about a cooking show?​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep your calm…​ ​​
​​​ ​Who asked you? Give me the remote!​ ​​
​​​ ​…You can watch it later!​ ​​
​​​ ​NO YOU!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​My favourite cartoons are on today! Gimme!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Phew!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoops!​ ​​
​​​ ​AH! WARU?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who cares, it’s just a bunch of comics.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bah! You’ll make more!​ ​​
​​​ ​More?​ ​​
​​​ ​MORE?!​ ​​
​​​ ​JUST A BUNCH OF CO…​ ​​
​​​ ​Why do I bother?..​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm!​ ​​
​​​ ​You think making comics is easy?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it not?​ ​​
​​​ ​If we consult history,​ ​​
​​​ ​the predecessors of comic books, such as medieval illustrations,​ ​​
​​​ ​Felice​ ​​
​​​ ​Deorlaf​ ​​
​​​ ​Dūstmǣġ​ ​​
​​​ ​Felice​ ​​
​​​ ​Deorlaf​ ​​
​​​ ​Dūstmǣġ​ ​​
​​​ ​Weard​ ​​
​​​ ​Deorlaf​ ​​
​​​ ​Dūstmǣġ​ ​​
​​​ ​Felice​ ​​
​​​ ​Deorlaf​ ​​
​​​ ​Weard​ ​​
​​​ ​Dūstmǣġ​ ​​
​​​ ​Deorlaf​ ​​
​​​ ​Weard​ ​​
​​​ ​Dūstmǣġ​ ​​
​​​ ​Deorlaf​ ​​
​​​ ​Weard​ ​​
​​​ ​Thirtēēn Cārds​ ​​
​​​ ​were a primitive form of entertainment for the…​ ​​
​​​ ​Brēol​ ​​
​​​ ​Gābriēl​ ​​
​​​ ​Spadu​ ​​
​​​ ​Rōma​ ​​
​​​ ​peasants.​ ​​
​​​ ​Need I remind you,​ ​​
​​​ ​that I’m here to get stupider!​ ​​
​​​ ​I just wanted to watch some cartoons…​ ​​
​​​ ​Exactly! D’ya hear what our Spongy friend said?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cartoons are cool, comics are SHI-…​ ​​
​​​ ​So, you’re saying YOU’LL do better than me?​ ​​
​​​ ​We’re literally your clones. You’ve literally called us up for this stuff.​ ​​
​​​ ​Weeell, if it’s that easy…​ ​​
​​​ ​…then all of you will make a comic each.​ ​​
​​​ ​The best one, in my…​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahem!​ ​​
​​​ ​opinion!​ ​​
​​​ ​…will choose what we’re gonna watch.​ ​​
​​​ ​(laughs)​ ​​
​​​ ​Pffft, who needs a remote!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck!​ ​​
​​​ ​ Phew! Well, that’ll keep them busy till the evening...​ ​​
​​​ ​I want this one! And this one!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHH, THIS ONE’S PRETTY!​ ​​
​​​ ​.​ ​​
​​​ ​..​ ​​
​​​ ​...​ ​​
​​​ ​Where’s all the paper?​ ​​
​​​ ​You can have toilet paper.​ ​​
​​​ ​WARU!​ ​​
​​​ ​I’ve thought up a masterpiece!​ ​​
​​​ ​And for that I need A LOT of paper!​ ​​
​​​ ​You’re not gonna need THESE anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aha! I’ll do something even better.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm…​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm… Comic books, comic books… What kinds are there?​ ​​
​​​ ​There’s some about safety, like in school!​ ​​
​​​ ​No! Too boring!​ ​​
​​​ ​Or maybe caricatures, like in the Punch magazine?...​ ​​
​​​ ​“Are we now​ ​​
​​ ​ in some alternative universe,​ ​​
​​ ​ where irony is king?”​ ​​
​​​ ​“Are we now​ ​​
​​ ​ in some alternative universe,​ ​​
​​ ​ where irony is king?”​ ​​
​​​ ​No! Too vulgar!​ ​​
​​​ ​Memes?​ ​​
​​​ ​Agh, still no!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes! I’ll have the best graphic novel!​ ​​
​​​ ​If I could learn how to draw…​ ​​
​​​ ​I can’t decide… What if Fёdor doesn’t like it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Edits!​ ​​
​​​ ​That’s such a huge responsibility!​ ​​
​​​ ​I need a partner.​ ​​
​​​ ​I need a partner...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm, it’s important to break the work into stages.​ ​​
​​ ​First…​ ​​
​​​ ​I must collect more data.​ ​​
​​​ ​«Comics:​ ​​
​​ ​Easy as ABC!»​ ​​
​​​ ​“Writer’s Manual”​ ​​
​​​ ​“Understanding Comics: ​ ​​
​​ ​The Invisible Art - ​ ​​
​​ ​Scott McCloud”​ ​​
​​​ ​“Understanding Comics: ​ ​​
​​ ​The Invisible Art - ​ ​​
​​ ​Scott McCloud”​ ​​
​​​ ​“Fundamentals of​ ​​
​​ ​ Character Design”​ ​​
​​​ ​“Drawing Cartoons​ ​​
​​ ​ And Comics for Dummies ”​ ​​
​​​ ​This isn’t enough!​ ​​
​​​ ​Um, like this? Do you like it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hm...​ ​​
​​​ ​yeah!.. It’s fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is something wrong? Should I fix anything?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm… give me that pencil.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, I see. Can I get back to work?​ ​​
​​​ ​Romeo?​ ​​
​​​ ​(giggles)​ ​​
​​​ ​(groaning in disgust)​ ​​
​​​ ​ОH!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Tense music)​ ​​
​​​ ​(evil laugh)​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sleeping in Fёdor’s bed?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you stealing someone else’s art?​ ​​
​​​ ​(Tense music)​ ​​
​​​ ​(evil laugh)​ ​​
​​​ ​I received power that our father never dreamed of!​ ​​
​​​ ​He was never your father!​ ​​
​​​ ​HUH?!​ ​​
​​​ ​…And then their swords cross!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, how’s it going?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! This is great. Just how I imagined it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, don’t mention it, I’m not…​ ​​
​​​ ​— I’m home!​ ​​
​​​ ​THE DEADLINE! QUICK!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look who I found.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who’s that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Gabriel! It’s been a while!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where was he?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhhhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Gabriel!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gabri! Gabri-Gabri-Gabri!​ ​​
​​​ ​You’re just in time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you finish the comic?​ ​​
​​​ ​Better than that! Look.​ ​​
​​​ ​Um… What… is that?​ ​​
​​​ ​I. Made. An animation!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why is it only three frames?​ ​​
​​​ ​DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS TO MAKE CARTOONS?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, alright, alright…​ ​​
​​​ ​Move over! King in the castle!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh wow! This is beautiful.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you copy the first result for “manga” on Google?​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAT?! No!​ ​​
​​​ ​The second?​ ​​
​​​ ​…Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahem! Who’s next?​ ​​
​​​ ​Woah…​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I should restrict your Internet access…​ ​​
​​​ ​That’s enough! It’s our turn.​ ​​
​​​ ​Get ready to read the most exciting saga about a fearless knight,​ ​​
​​​ ​whose heroic exploits are glorified by mankin-…​ ​​
​​​ ​(yawns)​ ​​
​​​ ​It’s a bit bland.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?..​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, it’s corny. It doesn’t hook you in.​ ​​
​​​ ​The characters’ motivation is unfounded!​ ​​
​​​ ​But, overall, it’s good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Especially compared to everyone else’s comics…​ ​​
​​​ ​AHH! There it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kuromaku, are you taking part?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, I just finished.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, so that’s your way of making comics... I thought you were writing a novel!​ ​​
​​​ ​Using statistical analysis, I have calculated the formula for the perfect comic.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm, impressive. And what are the results?​ ​​
​​​ ​The results are…​ ​​
​​​ ​Inconclusive.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, now I know.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm?​ ​​
​​​ ​I’m proud of you, guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought you’d give up on the idea, or turn the place upside down again,​ ​​
​​​ ​but you actually did great!​ ​​
​​​ ​And so, the rightful winner is the comic by Spade, and…​ ​​
​​​ ​Um…​ ​​
​​​ ​can I take part?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think we have a winner!..​ ​​
​​​ ​What the?...​ ​​
​​​ ​WOAH!​ ​​
​​​ ​It’s amazing!​ ​​
​​​ ​What a story! And all on one page!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this loss?​ ​​
​​​ ​IT’S BEAUTIFUL!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have to show it to the world!​ ​​
​​​ ​(All atonce)​ ​​
​​ ​WA-…​ ​​
​​​ ​(off-screen laughter)​ ​​
​​​ ​Ouch! Dang, Charlie! You’re a good shot!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I don’t even know how I did that! I’m sorry.​ ​​
​​​ ​How long do we have to watch this for?​ ​​
​​​ ​The whole season…​ ​​
​​​ ​(Waru sighs)​ ​​
​​​ ​(Gabriel giggles triumphantly.)​ ​​
​​​ ​(Фёдор зевает)​ ​​
​​​ ​AAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good sleep is the key to…​ ​​
​​​ ​JUST LEAVE!​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​